

MERN FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Hyemee Park

OBJECTIVE

I am Hyemee Park is proactive and detail-oriented Full-stack developer.

INTRODUCTION

I have worked as a web designer in South Korea and would like to learn further. With persistence and diligence, I have learned advanced front-end and back-end development. Also, I plan to achieve more concepts in the backend such as MySQL.

Persistence and diligence are my strong points that I am proud to have. These make me keep going through challenges and difficulties.

CONTACT

PHONE:

0402 - 096 - 632

WEBSITE:

https://www.codingpark.tech/

EMAIL:

Hyemee 1021@gmail.com

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hye-meepark/

GITHUB:

https://github.com/Hyemee1021

SKILLS

JavaScript React React Redux Node.js

EDUCATION

DENTED CODE

Mar 2023 - Jan 2024

I could learn coding skills to pursue my goal in the IT industry. For advanced front-end development, I learned JavaScript, React, React-Bootstrap, client-side validation, React-Redux, API integration, and React Router Dom.

For building the backend API server, I learned serverside validation such as JWT, Authentication, Authorization, Node.JS, Express.JS, and MongoDB. React Bootstrap CSS HTML Also, I have shared ideas and motivations with classmates while going through challenges to learn coding skills and get opportunities.

EXPERIENCE

COLES

Team member | Australia | 09 / 2021- present

Working in three different departments deli, meat, and bakery. I can adapt to changes quickly.

Also, I am used to working within a group and maintaining harmony with other team members from different age groups and all over the world.

MISO

Web designer | South Korea | 12/2020 – 05/2021

Working with front-end developers, I was in charge of maintaining and updating the company's websites and mobile website designs, using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript and editing main images with Photoshop. It was a good experience for me to work with backend and other frontend-developers

https://www.miso.center/
The above is the company's website.